Guide to the Mary (Mrs. Anson) Jones Letters
University of Houston Libraries
Mary (Mrs. Anson) Jones Letters
1858-1900
05/1970-003
Jones, Mary Smith
1.00 linear foot
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection contains 203 items and includes items dated from 1858 to 1900. The bulk of the items are dated between 1869 and 1881. The collection consists for the most part of correspondence, with some legal documents and tax papers.
Other Information: Uploaded to TARO, 2006. Additional information may be found at https://txarchives.org/uhsc/finding_aids/00034.xml
Biographical Information:
Mary Smith was born on July 24, 1819 in territory that later became Lawrence County, Arkansas. Her mother, a widow, moved her family to Brazoria County, Texas in 1834 when Mary was 15. The family settled on a farm in Brazoria County. Her mother married John Woodruff, a widower with several children. The Woodruff-Smith family left the farm during the Texas Revolution for safer regions farther east, returning after the Battle of San Jacinto.
Mary married Hugh McCrory on July 23, 1837 in Houston. McCrory was a soldier with Felix Huston's volunteers who became a Houston businessman following his release. McCrory died a few weeks after his marriage to Mary.
Mary met Anson Jones when he began boarding at the Woodruff house in Houston while he was serving in the Texas legislature. They planned to marry in 1838, following the end of Mary's year of mourning, but had to put aside their plans when Jones was appointed ambassador to the United States from Texas. Following his return the couple was married on May 17, 1840. Jones served as President of the Republic of Texas from 1844 to 1846, when Texas became part of the United States and James Pinkney Henderson became the first governor of the State of Texas.
Mary and Anson Jones had four children: Samuel Houston (later changed to Samuel Edward) (born [1841]), Charles Edward (born [1843]), Sallie S. (born [1845]), and Cromwell Anson (born [1849]). Jones committed suicide in January 1858, following a defeated bid to become the senator from Texas. Mary was widowed a second time at age 39.
Following Jones' death in 1858, Mary moved the family to Galveston, then to a farm in Harris County. Her husband had acquired land throughout east Texas during his life, and dealing with taxes, claims, and sales of the land occupied much of Mary's time throughout her life, as evidenced by her letters. She relied heavily on her children to assist her in her dealings with these legal and financial problems.
Samuel Edward and Charles served in the Confederate Army, where Charles died at the Battle of Shiloh. Samuel Edwards became a successful dentist. Sallie married R. G. Ashe and had at least one son, C. E. Ashe, who became a lawyer. Cromwell Anson became a lawyer and served as judge in Harris County, Texas until his death in 1888.
Mary became actively involved in the Daughters of the Republic of Texas, serving as its first president. She died on December 31, 1907. Her daughter, Sallie (Jones) Ashe, became an active member of the organization as well.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Genre/Form of Material:
Correspondence
Geographic Name:
Texas -- History -- 1846-1950
Personal Name:
Jones, C. Anson (Cromwell Anson), 1850-; Jones, Mary Smith
Acquisition Information:
Purchased by University of Houston in 1970 from Mrs. Grace David, The Bookman, 2243 San Felipe, Houston, TX
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Related Materials:
Mrs. Anson Jones Letters digital collection http://digital.lib.uh.edu/collection/p15195coll9
Scope and Contents
This collection contains 203 items and includes items dated from 1858 to 1900. The bulk of the items are dated between 1869 and 1881. The collection consists for the most part of correspondence, with some legal documents and tax papers.
In addition to Mary Jones' letters, there is correspondence from Sallie (Jones) Ashe, her husband R. G. Ashe, Henry Cowing, Anson Jones, Cromwell Anson Jones, Joseph E. Field, and J. J. McMillan.
The collection has been arranged in two series: Correspondence and Legal Documents. The Correspondence series includes 189 items, dating from 1858 to 1882. Mary Jones' letters, the bulk of the collection, are arranged chronologically. Following these letters are letters received from others, which have been arranged alphabetically by sender and chronologically within the group.
Transcripts are available in a binder in the reading room, as well as in the digital collection.
Detailed List of Contents
- Correspondence, 1866-1882
  Scope and Contents
  Most of the correspondence is from Mary Jones, primarily to her son Cromwell Anson Jones. These letters date between 1866 and 1882. The letters discuss local affairs and Mary Jones' life, as well as family members (Samuel Edward and Sallie S.) and friends. Many of the letters relate to problems with land claims and taxes on lands held by Mary Jones following the death of her husband.
  - Mary Jones to Colonel Thomas White, Galveston, March 29, 1866 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mary Jones to her sons, Willis, TX, April 3, [1869] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, TX, April 8, [1869] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Galveston, TX, May 8, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, July 11, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Galveston, July 18, [1869] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Galveston, July 19, [1869] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Galveston, July 23, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, July 29, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, August 13, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, September 5, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [October 3, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [October 17, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [October 24, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [November 7, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [November 23, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Galveston, on board Whitlane, [November 28, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, [December 11, 1869] (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, January 11, 1870 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [March 27, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [April 3, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [April 25, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [April 30, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [May 19, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 24)
    [With undated, unsigned note]
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [May 28, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, August 5, 1870 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [August] 13, 1870 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [September 29, 1870] (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, "At Gaston's", March 4, 1871 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, November 19, 1871 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, December 17, 1871 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, January 10, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, January 17, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, [January] 22, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, January 28, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, San Jacinto, March 29, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, May 25, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, October 22, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, October 24, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, November 25, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, San Jacinto, January 1873 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, April 18, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, June 11, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Headquarters, July 9, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, August 2, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, San Jacinto, January 25, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, June 25, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Near Dresden, July 24, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, August 20, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Dresden, September 3, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, October 13, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 23, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, San Jacinto, November 15, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 14, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 20, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, January 20, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [January 1875] (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, March 5, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, March 13, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 13, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 25, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, May 24, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, June 1, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, June 22, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, July 13, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, July 24, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, September 23, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, September 25, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, September 27, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 7, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 18, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [October, 1875] (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 9, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 12, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [December 20, 1875] (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 26, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 9, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 1, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, April 24, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 29, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, July 23, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [August 19, 1876] (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Montgomery County, Crystal, August 30, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Crystal, September 26, [1876] (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, March 12, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Gonzales County, Moulton, June 2, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Near Moulton, August 13, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Near Moulton, September 15, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, September 1877 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 5, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 6, 1877. (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 8, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 14, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 6, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 9, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 15, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 23, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 30, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, January 9, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, January 15, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 1, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 18, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, March 10, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, March 20, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 1, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 5, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, April 13, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, May 28, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, June 1, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, June 4, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, June 10, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, August 23, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, September 1, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, September 13, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, September 27, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 13, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 25, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, October 28, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 1, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 2, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 6, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 24, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 9, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 15, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 27, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 29, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, January 3, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [January] 8, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, January 23, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 4, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 14, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 17, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, February 25, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, March 11, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, May 22, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, July 19, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, October 12, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Dresden, October 30, [1879] (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Dresden, November 1, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 14, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [December] 16, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, [] 27, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [January 7, 1880] (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, November 6, [1880] (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, November 8, [1880] (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, November 12, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 23, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 25, [1880] (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, November 26, [1880] (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, November 28, [1880] (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, November 30, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, December 3, [1880] (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [December 5, 1880] (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 7, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, December 15, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, May 24, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Sour Lake, July 7, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, July 9, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, [Sour Lake], [July 12, 1881] (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Sour Lake, July 14, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Sour Lake, July 16, [1881] (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Sour Lake, July 26, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Gonzales Company, near Moulton, September 13, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Mary Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones, Near Moulton, September 19, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Letters, undated; 10 items (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Parts of letters, undated; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - R. G. [Gaston] Ashe to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 27, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Sallie (Jones) Ashe to Cromwell Anson Jones, Lynchburg, September 8, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Sallie (Jones) Ashe to Cromwell Anson Jones, Willis, November 16, 1875 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Sallie (Jones) Ashe to Cromwell Anson Jones, Crystal Creek, April 24, 1876 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Henry Cowing to Mary Jones, [1872-1873] (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Joseph E. Field to Mary Jones, Lavaca, November 14, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Joseph E. Field to Mary Jones, Lavaca, December 29, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Joseph E. Field to Mary Jones, Lavaca, January 10, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Joseph E. Field to Mary Jones [copy]; Anson Jones to Cromwell Anson Jones [copy], [1867]; approximately 1858 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Cromwell Anson Jones, Houston, October 7, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - J. J. McMillan, Harris County, Cedar Bayou, October 18, 1875 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Legal Documents, 1858-1900
  There are only 15 items in the series. Included are property taxes, land deeds, powers of attorney, and other miscellaneous legal papers. The materials date from 1858 to 1900, with the bulk of the items between 1890 and 1900.
  - Property Taxes, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Property Taxes, 1860 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Property Taxes, 1862 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Property Taxes, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Property Taxes, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Property Taxes, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Deed of Land - Montgomery County, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Power of Attorney, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Deed of Land - Harris County, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Deed of Land - Harris County, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Deed of Land - Harris County, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Court Summons Citation - Harris County, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Announcement of Property Sale - Harris County, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Law Suit - San Jacinto County, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Property List, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)